Guide to the John Farquhar Fulton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Files, 1910-1960; Series I
  - American Journal of Physiology, 1925-1945 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - American Journal of Roentgenology and RadiumTherapy, 1931-1950 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - American Library Association: Joint Committee on Importations, 1939-1943 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - American Medical Association
    General note
    See also: box 158, Folder 2260
    - 1926-1934 (Box 4, Folder 60-61)
    - 1935-1959 (Box 5, Folder 62-65)
  - American Medical Writers' Association, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - American Men of Science, 1927-1948 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1931, 1938-1947 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - American Neurological Association, 1932-1960 (Box 5, Folder 69-74)
    See also: box 168, Folder 2411
  - American Oxonian, 1926-1958 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - American Philosophical Society
    - General, 1939-1960 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Franklin Papers, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Publications Committee
      - General, 1950-1960 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Adelmann Manuscript, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Cohen Manuscript, 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Herrick Manuscript, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Kisch Manuscript, 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - MacKinney Manuscript, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Special Committee [on funds], 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - American Physiological Society, 1930-1952 (Box 6, Folder 85-87)
  - American Physiological Society: Survey of Physiological Science, 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 88-89)
  - American Psychiatric Association, 1939-1951 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - American Psychosomatic Association, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - American Public Health Association, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - American Red Cross, 1940-1945 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - American Review of Soviet Medicine, 1943-1947 (Box 7, Folder 94-95)
  - American Scientific, Medical, and TechnicalBibliography, 1946-1947
    See: Series II, box 231, Folder 534
  - American Society for Research in Psychosomatic Problems, 1943-1949 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - American Society of Electroencephalography, 1947-1958 (Box 7, Folder 97-99)
  - American Society of ammalogists, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - American Society of the French Legion of Honor, 1950-1960 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - American Society of Tropical Medicine, 1939-1948 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - American Society of Zoologists, 1925-1959 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - American Surgical Association, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - American-Swiss Foundation, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - America's Young Men, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Anand, Bal Krishnan, 1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 107-108)
  - Anderson, Claude T., 1948-1950, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Anderson, Rudolph J., 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Andrade, Edward Neville da Costa, 1949-1959 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Andrus, E. Cowles, 1925, 1929, 1940-1944 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    See also: box 237-240, Folders 640-687
  - Anesthesiology, 1947-1951 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Angell, James R., 1930-1940 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    See also: box 187, Folder 2887
  - Angier, Roswell P., 1932-1934 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Annales de physiologie et de physicochimiebiologique, 1934-1938 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Annals of Medical History, 1927-1937 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Annals of Science, 1935-1937 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Annual Review of Physiology
    - 1936-1949 (Box 8, Folder 119-121)
    - 1950-1953, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc.
    - General, 1946-1952 (Box 9, Folder 123-124)
    - Agenda, minutes, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Reports, 1946-1950 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Anthropoid Ape Research Foundation, 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Apperly, Frank, 1934-1942 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Archeion, 1929-1939 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Archives internationales de physiologie, 1934-1938 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Archives of Neurology and Psychiatry, 1926-1939 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Archivos Argentinos de Neurologia, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Arhanić, Ruža, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    See also: box 112, folder 1540
  - Aring, Charles D.
    - 1934-1938 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - 1939-1960 (Box 10, Folder 135-136)
  - Armstrong, Harry G., 1933, 1943-1952 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Armstrong, John M., 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Army Medical Library
    See: box 195-207, folders 1-197
  - Ascenzi, Antonio, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Ascroft, Peter B., 1935-1953 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Asher, Leon, 1929-1936 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Ashley-Montagu, M. F.
    See: box 125, folders 1718-1719
  - Ask-Upmark, Erik, 1933-1955 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Diseases
    See: box 198-200, Folders 31-52
  - Association of American Colleges, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Association of Medical Students, 1938-1941 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Association of Military Surgeons, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Association of Scientific Workers, 1928-1933 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Atlantic Monthly Press, 1939-1941, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Atterbury, Grosvenor and Astelle, 1944-1946, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Audiology Foundation, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Avicenna Society, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Aydelotte, Frank, 1934-1956 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    See also: box 69, folders 959-960 See also: boxes 148-149, folders 2015-2024
  - Bab-Bag (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Bai-Bak (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Bal-Bam (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Ban-Barn (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Barr-Barz (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Bas-Bay (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Bea-Bec (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Bed-Bel (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Bena-Bent (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Berg-Bert (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Bes-Bio (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Bir-Blai (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Blak-Blu (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Boa-Bold (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Boll-Bor (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Bos-Boy (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - Bra-Bre (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Bri-Bros (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Brou-Bry (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Bub-Bun (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - Bur-By (Box 12, Folder 172)
  - Baetjer, Anne N., 1930-1946 (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Bagdasar, Dimitri and Florica, 1928-1937, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - Bailey, Percival, 1928-1960 (Box 13, Folder 175-179)
  - Bainton, Roland H., 1931-1954 (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - Baltimore City Medical Society, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 181)
  - Ban, Tadaysu, 1951-1955 (Box 13, Folder 182)
  - Banks, William N., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 182a)
  - Banta Publishing Company
    See: box 68, folders 945-951
  - Barach, Alvan L., 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 183)
  - Barbour, Henry G., 1930-1936 (Box 13, Folder 184)
  - Barclay, A. E., 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 185-187)
  - Barclays Bank, Ltd., 1930 (Box 13, Folder 188)
  - Barcroft, Henry, 1947-1954 (Box 13, Folder 189)
  - Bard, Philip, 1928-1952 (Box 14, Folder 190-192)
  - Barker, Creighton, 1933-1952 (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - Barker, David, 1949-1958 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - Barker, Lewellys F., 1931-1935 (Box 14, Folder 195)
  - Barnard, Cyril C., 1936, 1948-1951 (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - Barnard, Edward T., 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 197)
  - Barnes, T. Cunliffe, 1936-1959 (Box 14, Folder 198)
  - Barney, Mabel, 1921-1923 (Box 14, Folder 199)
  - Barris, Ralph W., 1936-1938 (Box 14, Folder 200)
  - Barron, Donald, 1933-1958 (Box 14, Folder 201)
    See also: box 222, folders 399
  - Bartlett, Henrietta, 1934, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 202)
  - Baruch Committee on Physical Medicine, 1944-1951 (Box 14, Folder 203-205)
  - Batson, Oscar V., 1931, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 206)
  - Baumgartner, Leona
    - 1931-1942 (Box 15, Folder 207-214)
    - 1943-1960, undated (Box 16, Folder 215-221)
  - Baumgartner, William J., 1939-1941 (Box 16, Folder 222)
  - Baxter, Neal, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 223)
  - Bayne, Helen, 1935-1945, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 224)
  - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope, 1932-1959 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    See also: boxes 188-189, folders 2902-2908
  - Bayne-Jones Portrait Fund, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 226)
  - Bean, William B., 1948-1950, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 228)
  - Beard, Rodney, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 229)
  - Beattie, John, 1929-1947 (Box 17, Folder 230-231)
  - Beaumont Club
    - General, 1930-1959 (Box 17, Folder 232)
    - Caulfield Paper, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 233)
    - Lebanon Meeting House, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 234)
  - Beaumont Memorial Foundation, 1934, 1954, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 235)
  - Beck, Julian, 1938-1940 (Box 17, Folder 236-237)
  - Beecher, Henry K., 1937-1946, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 238)
  - Behnke, Albert R., 1940-1947 (Box 17, Folder 239)
  - Bell, Whitfield J., 1953-1960 (Box 17, Folder 240-241)
  - Belloni, Luigi, 1949, 1953-1959 (Box 17, Folder 242)
  - Belt, Elmer, 1934-1960 (Box 18, Folder 243)
  - Bender, Morris B., 1936-1960 (Box 18, Folder 244-246)
  - Bendheim, Otto L., 1937 (Box 18, Folder 247)
  - Bénecke, P. V. M., 1932-1934 (Box 18, Folder 248)
  - Benedict, Francis G., 1928-1937 (Box 18, Folder 249)
  - Benford, Robert, 1947-1960 (Box 18, Folder 250)
  - Benjamin, John M., 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 251)
  - Bennett, Michael, 1953-1957 (Box 18, Folder 252)
  - Benson, Otis J., 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - Berg, Carol, 1938-1954 (Box 18, Folder 254)
  - Berg, Leonard F., 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 255)
  - Berg, Margaret Fulton, 1931-1958 (Box 18, Folder 256-257)
  - Berger, Knute E., 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 258)
  - Berglund, Hilding, 1930-1948 (Box 18, Folder 259)
  - Berkson, Joseph, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 260)
  - Berman, Aaron Joseph, 1949-1959 (Box 18, Folder 261)
  - Bermuda Biological Station, 1926, 1930-1932, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 262)
    See also: Folder 1623
  - Bernstein, Albion O., 1934-1935 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Bernstein, Henry, 1956-1959 (Box 19, Folder 264)
  - Best, Charles, 1935-1944, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 265)
  - Bett, Walter R., 1928-1939, 1947-1959 (Box 19, Folder 266)
    See also: box 136, folders 1843-1844
  - Bibliographical Society, 1928-1960 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Bibliographical Society of America, 1933-1942, 1950-1958 (Box 19, Folder 268)
  - Bieber, Irving, 1933-1960 (Box 19, Folder 269)
  - Biological Abstracts, 1926-1943 (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - Bishop, George H., 1926-1961 (Box 19, Folder 271-272)
  - Bishop, W. J., 1947, 1952-1959 (Box 19, Folder 273)
  - Bixler, Elizabeth, 1948-1958 (Box 19, Folder 274)
  - Black, Samuel P. W., 1947-1957 (Box 19, Folder 275)
  - Blake, John B., 1952-1960 (Box 19, Folder 276)
  - Blake, William D., 1945-1960 (Box 20, Folder 277)
    See also: box 222, folder 401
  - Bligh, Eric W., 1923-1958
    See: box 202, folders 83-91
  - Bloom, Walter, 1947, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Bloomer, William E., 1943-1957 (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Bluestone, E. M, 1949, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - Blum, John M., 1958 (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Blumer, George, 1931-1960 (Box 20, Folder 282-283)
  - Blumgart, Hermann, 1927, 1942, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 284)
  - Boas Memorial Essay, 1955-1960 (Box 20, Folder 285)
  - Boase, Tom S. R., 1955-1960 (Box 20, Folder 286)
  - Bodkin, Thomas, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 287)
  - Bodleian Library, 1929-1957 (Box 20, Folder 288)
  - Boeing Aircraft Company, 1942, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 289)
    See also: boxes 237-240, folders 640-687
  - Bonelli, Maria Luisa, 1955-1960 (Box 20, Folder 290)
  - Bonin, Gerhardt von
    See: box 174, folder 2603
  - Booraem, Edith
    See: box 116, folder 1582
  - Booraem, Harold, 1931-1937 (Box 20, Folder 291)
  - Booraem, Laura Fulton
    - 1929-1938 (Box 20, Folder 292-293)
    - 1939-1951 (Box 21, Folder 294-298)
  - Booraem, Laura Fulton [daughter of Laura Fulton Booraem], 1944-1956 (Box 21, Folder 299)
    - Bazett, H. Cuthbert, 1925-1946 (Box 16, Folder 227)
  - Boothby, Walter M., 1941-1947 (Box 21, Folder 300)
  - Boring, Edwin G., 1934-1946 (Box 21, Folder 301)
  - Bornstein, Walter S., 1937-1960 (Box 22, Folder 302)
  - Boston Globe, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 303)
  - Boston Medical History Club, 1927-1936 (Box 22, Folder 304)
  - Boston Medical Library, 1925-1955 (Box 22, Folder 305-306)
  - Bott, E. A., 1940 (Box 22, Folder 307)
  - Botterell, E. Harry, 1935-1955 (Box 22, Folder 308-309)
  - Boyd, Julian P., 1947-1952 (Box 22, Folder 310)
  - Braatoy, Trygve, 1949-1954 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Brain, 1928-1945 (Box 22, Folder 312)
  - Brain, Russell, 1929-1960 (Box 22, Folder 313)
  - Brand, Jeanne H., 1953-1960 (Box 22, Folder 314)
  - Brasch, Fredrick E., 1933-1947 (Box 23, Folder 315)
    See also: box 79, folders 1116-1119 See also: box 81, folders 1137-1142
  - Bray, A. W., 1932-1941 (Box 23, Folder 316)
  - Brazier, Mary A. B., 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 317)
  - Bremer, Frederic, 1925-1960 (Box 23, Folder 318)
  - Brendler, Samuel J., 1947-1953 (Box 23, Folder 319)
  - Brickner, Richard M., 1934-1943 (Box 23, Folder 320)
  - Brightman, Milton W., 1948-1959 (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - Briscoe, Grace, 1924-1934 (Box 23, Folder 322)
  - British Medical Journal, 1927-1943 (Box 23, Folder 323)
  - British Museum, 1927-1931, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 324)
  - British Supply Council, 1941-1942 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Brobeck, John R., 1944-1959 (Box 23, Folder 326)
    See also: box 222, Folder 402
  - Brockett, Susan, 1932-1935 (Box 23, Folder 327)
  - Brodman, Estelle, 1944-1954 (Box 23, Folder 328)
    See also: boxes 122-123, folders 1668-1673
  - Bronk, Detlev, 1930-1959 (Box 23, Folder 329-331)
    See also: box 232-236, folders 545-635
  - Brooks, Chandler, 1931-1957 (Box 23, Folder 332)
  - Brouwer, Bernardus, 1930-1940 (Box 23, Folder 333)
  - Brown, Dugald E. S., 1930-1938 (Box 23, Folder 334)
  - Brown, M. Hunter, 1937-1939 (Box 23, Folder 335)
  - Bruhn, John M., 1932-1950 (Box 24, Folder 336-337)
  - Bucaille, Maurice, 1955-1960 (Box 24, Folder 338)
  - Buchanan, Douglas, 1955-1960 (Box 24, Folder 339)
  - Buchanan, Douglas N., 1924-1927 (Box 24, Folder 340)
  - Buchstein, Harold F., 1938-1947 (Box 24, Folder 341)
  - Buchthal, Fritz, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 342)
  - Buck, Peter H., 1938-1951 (Box 24, Folder 343)
  - Buck, Solon, 1943-1945 (Box 24, Folder 344)
    See also: box 240-246, folders 706-766
  - Buck, Warren E., 1951-1954 (Box 24, Folder 345)
  - Bucy, Paul C.
    - 1930-1944 (Box 24, Folder 346-349)
    - 1945-1960 (Box 25, Folder 350)
  - Buess, Henrich, 1951-1960 (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - Bulletin of the New York Academy ofMedicine, 1929-1939 (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - Bumstead, John H., 1949-1959 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - Burch, Frank E., 1925-1934 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - Burchard, John E., 1947-1960 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Burlingame, Charles C., 1936, 1946-1950 (Box 25, Folder 356)
  - Burr, Harold S., 1930-1938, 1950-1960 (Box 25, Folder 357)
  - Burrage, Walter L., 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 358)
  - Burrell, Virginia, 1934-1945, 1953, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 359)
  - Burrow, Trigant, 1939, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 360)
  - Butler, Charlotte S., 1935-1938 (Box 25, Folder 361)
  - Butler, Elmer, 1944-1946 (Box 25, Folder 362)
  - Butterfield, Lyman H., 1946-1954, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 363)
  - Cab-Cap (Box 25, Folder 364)
  - Car-Cax (Box 25, Folder 365)
  - Ce-Cha (Box 26, Folder 366)
  - Che-Chu (Box 26, Folder 367)
  - Cl (Box 26, Folder 368)
  - Cob-Col (Box 26, Folder 369)
  - Com-Con (Box 26, Folder 370)
  - Coo-Cox (Box 26, Folder 371)
  - Cr (Box 26, Folder 372)
  - Cu (Box 26, Folder 373)
  - C. V. Mosby Co.
    See: box 126, folder 1734
  - Cabagnot, Paciano and Gregorio, 1938-1948 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - Cairns, Hugh, 1927-1953 (Box 27, Folder 375-383)
    See also: box 236, folder 631 See also: box 247, folders 787-791
  - California Academy of Medicine, 1934, 1947-1950 (Box 27, Folder 384)
  - Callender, George, 1943-1946 (Box 28, Folder 385-386)
    See also: box 247, folders 789-791
  - Calver, George W., 1942-1946 (Box 28, Folder 387)
  - Calvert, Phyllis, 1947-1948, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 388)
  - Cambridge Instrument Company, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 389)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1930-1954 (Box 28, Folder 390)
  - Campbell, Eldridge, 1931-1956 (Box 28, Folder 391)
  - Campbell, J. Menzies, 1952-1960 (Box 28, Folder 392)
  - Campbell, James, 1940-1960 (Box 28, Folder 393-394)
  - Canadian Medical Association Journal, 1929-1932 (Box 28, Folder 395)
  - Candela, P. B., 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 396)
  - Canfield, Norton, 1942-1959 (Box 28, Folder 397)
  - Cannon, Bradford, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 398)
  - Cannon, Walter B., 1925-1951 (Box 28, Folder 399-401)
  - Cappiello, Robert, 1943-1951 (Box 29, Folder 402)
  - CARE Inc., 1949-1959 (Box 29, Folder 403-406)
  - Carleton, Harry, 1928-1931 (Box 29, Folder 407)
  - Carlson, A. J., 1931-1950 (Box 29, Folder 408)
  - Carmichael, E. Arnold, 1935-1940, 1947-1956 (Box 29, Folder 409)
  - Carmichael, Leonard, 1927-1959 (Box 29, Folder 410)
  - Carpenter, C. R., 1937-1939 (Box 29, Folder 411)
  - Carroll, Frank D., 1932-1933, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 412)
  - Carson, Leon D., 1942-1950 (Box 29, Folder 413)
  - Carter, John, 1932-1938, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 414)
  - Cary, Melbert, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 415)
  - Cass, Caroll, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 416)
  - Cass, R. Elizabeth, 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 417)
  - Castiglioni, Vittorio, 1953-1957 (Box 29, Folder 418)
  - Castle, William B., 1929-1941, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 419)
  - Catchpole, Hubert, 1938-1959 (Box 29, Folder 420-421)
  - Cate, Jasper ten, 1935-1939, 1953, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 422)
  - Cattell, McKeen, 1932-1955 (Box 30, Folder 423)
  - Caulfield, Ernest, 1935-1947 (Box 30, Folder 424)
  - Cawadias, A. P., 1941-1956 (Box 30, Folder 425)
  - Century Association, 1931-1959 (Box 30, Folder 426)
  - Chalmers, Gordon K., 1931-1954 (Box 30, Folder 427-428)
    See also: box 98, folder 1357
  - Chambers, Robert, 1929-1932, 1943-1952 (Box 30, Folder 429)
  - Champion, Louise, 1947-1957 (Box 30, Folder 430)
  - Chance, Burton, 1941-1953 (Box 30, Folder 431)
  - Chang, Hsiang-Tung, 1943-1960 (Box 30, Folder 432-434)
  - Chapin, Adele, 1929-1938 (Box 30, Folder 435)
  - Chapin, Susan, 1929-1955 (Box 31, Folder 436)
  - Chapman, Robert W., 1930-1952 (Box 31, Folder 437-438)
  - Chapman, Sarah W., 1935-1939, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 439)
  - Charles C. Thomas, Publisher
    See also: box 184, Folders 2727-2728 See also: box 310, folder 114
    - General
      - 1927-1933 February (Box 31, Folder 440-447)
      - 1933 March-1937 (Box 32, Folder 448-456)
      - 1938-1952 (Box 33, Folder 457-467)
      - 1953-1960 (Box 34, Folder 468-469)
    - Adolph's manuscript, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 470)
    - Bailey's Intracranial Tumors, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 471)
    - Beaumont facsimile, 1934-1946 (Box 34, Folder 472)
    - Beutner's manuscript, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 473)
    - Boas's manuscript, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 474)
    - Bulletin of the Neurological Institute, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 475)
    - Castiglioni translation, 1932-1933 (Box 34, Folder 476)
    - Cushing's books, 1931-1932 (Box 34, Folder 477)
    - d'Irsay's Physiology, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 478)
    - Engelback's Endocrine Medicine, 1931-1933 (Box 34, Folder 479)
    - Favill manuscript, 1932-1933 (Box 34, Folder 480)
    - Franklin's Fabricius, 1929-1934 (Box 34, Folder 481-483)
    - Franklin's Monograph on Veins, 1934-1937 (Box 34, Folder 484)
    - Grinker's Neurology, 1932-1943 (Box 34, Folder 485)
    - Grollman's Cardiac Output, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 486)
    - Hitchcock manuscript, 1929-1935 (Box 34, Folder 487)
    - Homan's Surgery, 1930-1939 (Box 34, Folder 488)
    - Leake's translation of Harvey's De MotuCordis, 1928-1939 (Box 35, Folder 489-490)
    - Livngston's Clinical Aspects of VisceralNeurology, 1932-1935 (Box 35, Folder 491)
    - Major's Clinical Readings, 1930-1931 (Box 35, Folder 492)
    - Payne Stone Age collection, 1931-1939 (Box 35, Folder 493-495)
    - Physiological and Pharmacological monographs, 1928-1931 (Box 35, Folder 496)
    - Ruhrah's Osler, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 497)
    - Sheehan manuscript, 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 498)
    - Spurling manuscript, 1933-1935 (Box 35, Folder 499)
    - Thompson manuscript, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 500)
    - Thom's Classical Contributions to Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1931-1936 (Box 35, Folder 501)
    - Wayne-Finch's Syphillis, 1934-1935 (Box 35, Folder 502)
    - Withering facsimile, 1930-1934 (Box 35, Folder 503)
    - Withington reprint, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 504)
    - Yale University Press, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 505)
    - Yerkes' manuscript, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 506)
  - Charlton, H.B., 1950, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 507)
  - Chatfield, C. M., 1927-1929 (Box 36, Folder 508)
  - Cheetham, Richard W. S., 1942-1953 (Box 36, Folder 509)
  - Chi Psi Fraternity, 1925, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 510)
  - Chidsey, Jane L., 1932-1943 (Box 36, Folder 511)
  - Childs, Starling W., 1938-1944 (Box 36, Folder 512)
  - Choate School, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 513)
  - Cholst, Sheldon, 1947-1950 (Box 36, Folder 514)
  - Christian, Henry A., 1936-1939, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 515)
  - Churchill, Edward, 1941-1960 (Box 36, Folder 516)
  - Chute, Richard, 1931-1942, 1953-1960 (Box 36, Folder 517)
  - Ciba Pharmaceutical Products, Inc., 1954-1957 (Box 36, Folder 518)
  - Clarendon Press, 1952-1959 (Box 36, Folder 519)
  - Clark, Charles Upson, 1943, 1955-1960 (Box 36, Folder 520)
  - Clark, Dean A., 1927-1953 (Box 36, Folder 521-523)
  - Clark, Orton Loring, 1948-1951 (Box 36, Folder 524)
  - Clark, Wilfred E. LeGros, 1929-1956 (Box 36, Folder 525-526)
  - Clarke, Clement C., 1937-1942, 1952-1958 (Box 36, Folder 527)
  - Clarke, Robert W., 1936-1959 (Box 36, Folder 528-529)
    See also: box 223, folder 403
  - Clausman, Gilbert J., 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 530)
  - Clemons, Albert A., 1927-1937 (Box 37, Folder 531)
  - Clendening, Logan, 1937-1957 (Box 37, Folder 532-534)
  - Cleverdon, Douglas, 1933-1936 (Box 37, Folder 535)
  - Club of Odd Volumes, 1948-1958 (Box 37, Folder 536)
  - Cobb, Stanley, 1924-1956 (Box 37, Folder 537-539)
  - Codding, Mildred, 1928-1932, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 540)
  - Code, Charles F., 1942-1946 (Box 37, Folder 541)
    See also: box 237-239, folders 640-686
  - Coffee House Club, 1931-1935 (Box 37, Folder 542)
  - Coffin, Charles M., 1938-1941, 1949-1952 (Box 37, Folder 543)
  - Coggeshall, Howard, 1935 (Box 37, Folder 544)
  - Cohen, Henry, 1937, 1952-1960 (Box 37, Folder 545)
  - Cohen, I. Bernard
    See also: boxes 79-82, folders 1116-1145
    - 1941-1948 (Box 37, Folder 546)
    - 1949-1959 (Box 38, Folder 547-549)
  - Cohen, Leonard A., 1948-1959 (Box 38, Folder 550)
  - Cohn, Alfred E., 1933-1946 (Box 38, Folder 551)
  - Cohn, Edwin J., 1926-1934, 1944-1953 (Box 38, Folder 552)
  - Cole, F. J., 1937-1959 (Box 38, Folder 553)
  - Coley, Bradley L., 1948-1949 (Box 38, Folder 554)
  - Colish, A., 1943 (Box 38, Folder 555)
    See also: box 248-250, folders 806-825
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 556)
  - Collip, J. B., 1930-1949, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 557)
  - Colman, Elizabeth S., 1931-1942 (Box 38, Folder 558)
  - Colonial Society of Massachusetts, 1933-1934, 1949-1958 (Box 38, Folder 559)
  - Coloviras, George J., 1941-1945 (Box 38, Folder 560)
  - Colp, Ralph Jr., 1950-1959 (Box 38, Folder 561)
  - Columbia University Press, 1947-1949 (Box 39, Folder 562)
  - Comité Belge d'Histoire des Sciences, 1951-1960 (Box 39, Folder 563)
  - Commission on Liberal Education, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 564)
  - Committee for National Morale, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 565)
  - Committee on Records of War Administration, 1944
    See: box 170, folder 2441
  - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 566)
  - Comroe, Julius H., Jr., 1943-1956 (Box 39, Folder 567)
  - Conference on Science in General Education, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 568)
  - Congresso Nazioale di Storia della Medicina, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 569)
  - Conklin, Edwin G., 1949 (Box 39, Folder 570)